{"questionList":[{"question":"Where is the position of home button?","answerList":[{"key":1,"answer":"It\u2019s located on lower the part of the phone."},{"key":2,"answer":"It\u2019s located on lower part the of the phone."},{"key":3,"answer":"It's located on the lower part of the phone."},{"key":4,"answer":"It\u2019s located lower the part on of the phone."}],"correct":3},{"question":"Where is the position of touch screen?","answerList":[{"key":1,"answer":"It\u2019s located on front the surface."},{"key":2,"answer":"It\u2019s located on the front surface."},{"key":3,"answer":"It\u2019s located on the surface front."},{"key":4,"answer":"It\u2019s located front on the surface"}],"correct":2},{"question":"Where is the position of volume button?","answerList":[{"key":1,"answer":"It\u2019s located on the right side of the phone."},{"key":2,"answer":"It\u2019s located on right the side of the phone."},{"key":3,"answer":"It\u2019s located on the side right of the phone."},{"key":4,"answer":" It\u2019s located side on the right of the phone."}],"correct":1},{"question":"Where is the position of front camera?","answerList":[{"key":1,"answer":"It\u2019s located the upper right over surface."},{"key":2,"answer":" It\u2019s located over the surface upper right"},{"key":3,"answer":"It\u2019s located over the right upper surface."},{"key":4,"answer":"It\u2019s located over the upper right surface."}],"correct":4},{"question":"Where is the position of sleep\/wake button?","answerList":[{"key":1,"answer":"It\u2019s located on the upper left corner of the phone."},{"key":2,"answer":"It\u2019s located on the left upper corner of the phone"},{"key":3,"answer":"It\u2019s located on upper the left corner of the phone."},{"key":4,"answer":" It\u2019s located on upper left the corner of the phone."}],"correct":1},{"question":"Where is the position of status bar?","answerList":[{"key":1,"answer":" It\u2019s located on the left upper surface."},{"key":2,"answer":" It\u2019s located on the upper left surface."},{"key":3,"answer":"It\u2019s located on upper the left surface."},{"key":4,"answer":"It\u2019s located on upper left the surface."}],"correct":2},{"question":"Where is the position of SIM card tray?","answerList":[{"key":1,"answer":"It\u2019s located in the middle part of the side left of the phone."},{"key":2,"answer":" It\u2019s located in the part middle of the side left of the phone."},{"key":3,"answer":" It\u2019s located in the middle part of the left side of the phone."},{"key":4,"answer":"It\u2019s located in the part middle of the left side of the phone."}],"correct":3},{"question":"Where is the position of dock connector?","answerList":[{"key":1,"answer":"It\u2019s located in between the speaker and the microphone."},{"key":2,"answer":"It\u2019s located between in the speaker and the microphone."},{"key":3,"answer":"It\u2019s located in between speaker the and the microphone."},{"key":4,"answer":"It\u2019s located in between the speaker and microphone the."}],"correct":1},{"question":"Where is the position of speaker?","answerList":[{"key":1,"answer":"It\u2019s located on the lower corner right of the phone."},{"key":2,"answer":" It\u2019s located on the corner lower right of the phone"},{"key":3,"answer":"It\u2019s located on the right lower corner of the phone."},{"key":4,"answer":" It\u2019s located on the lower right corner of the phone."}],"correct":4},{"question":"Where is the position of camera lens?","answerList":[{"key":1,"answer":"It\u2019s located on the left upper corner of the phone."},{"key":2,"answer":" It\u2019s located on the upper left corner of the phone."},{"key":3,"answer":" It\u2019s located on the corner upper left of the phone."},{"key":4,"answer":" It\u2019s located on upper the left corner of the phone."}],"correct":2}]}